Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative records, Series 13
  - CFO records, Series 13 subseries 5
    - Revies FI/02, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Staff Positions - Dev, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Financial Budget, 2004; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Financial - Prior FY Reports Monthly, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Celebration of Life - Albert Uster and Leonard B. "Bud" Doggett, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Property Tax Docs, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - DNC Wire Info, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Purchase Procedure Accounting, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Accounting Procedures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Finance Policy, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Reusch International, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Audit Planning, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Independent Contractor Rules Accounting Procedures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Finance - Tax Exempt Funding, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Chart of Accounts, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Maya Lin, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 49)
    - Eggleston, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 50)
    - Exhibitions, 2010; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 51)
    - Labor Budget, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 52)
    - College Enrollment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 53)
    - Restricted Ddefinitions, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 54)
    - Capital Expenditures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 77, Folder 55)
    - Gehry Planning, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Facilities Program Pre-Schematics Phase, 2000 January 18; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Design Program for the Corcoran Gallery of Art- Malesardi Steiner Keyes McCommons Architects, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - National Capitol Children's Museum, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Transition Planning Gehry, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Newman, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Energy Control, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Gehry- Admissions, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Andersen Model, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Chillum, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran Budget Information, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Planning Commission Public Hearing, 2007; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Financial Update, 2007; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Final Report Confidential The Corcoran Gallery of Art Internal Assessment Prepared by Carol O'Brien Associates, 1999; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Request for Proposal the Corcoran Gallery of Art- Cafes and Catering Services Descriptive Information, 2002; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - AAM Re-Accreditation Final Report, 2007; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Confidential- Settlement Information, Email, and Legal Paperwork, 2006; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Jeanne D'Arc Exhibition- Wheelchair Accessibility Complaint, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Neri Works loans, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Rex Weil- Confidential, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - The Bonner Group, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - ABT College IT, 1999-2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Guardsmark Security, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Misc. Paperwork, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - National Landmark Status, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Existing Roof Systems Report and Recommendations Including Photographic Tour, 1990; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Master's Thesis "An Unjust Legacy: A Critical Study of the Political Campaigns of William Andrews Clark 1888-1901" by Stan Pitts, 2006; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - ECS LLC- Phase I Environmental Site Assessment Corcoran School of Art and Design At Fillmore School, 2006; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Occupancy Permit Study for the Corcoran Gallery of Art- Malesardi Stiener Keyes McCommons Architects, 1999; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Hazardous Materials Abatement General Specification Requirements Volume 1 of 2 The Fillmore School, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Quinn Evans Architects- Records of Transittal, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Hazardous Materials Abatement General Specification Requirements Volume 2 of 2 The Fillmore School, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - The Corcoran School of Art Rehabilitation of the Fillmore School Specifications Design Development Package 22 April 1998, Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - 10 Year Plan- Long Range, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Finance Report, 2005; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Finance Report, 2004; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Finance Report, 2003; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Financial/Budget Reports, 1997-2003; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting- Aramark Role of the Center, 1997; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Rationale and explanation for proposed ARAMARK planning process, 1997; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Accounting and Auditing Development, 1998; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Direct Deposit, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran Museum of Art, College of Art & Design Campaign Feasibility Study, 2005; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Investment Policies, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - The Corcoran Museum and School of Art Information Technology Vision, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Preconstruction Costs, 1999; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Architectural Selection, 1999; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Gehry Resolution, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - A Meeting of Architectural Selection Panel B, 1998; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Mid-Schematic Cost Model, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - HR: Position Refilled, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Campaign for the Corcoran, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Millennium Projections, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Building Press, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - 9/24 Board Meeting, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Interview for Renovation Architectural Services for the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2002; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - JBK Council Meetings, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Jurow Schol, Mae W. School Projects Scholarships, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Chillum Renovation, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - CCAD Transition Space, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Finance Committee, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Kennedy Rosalts, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition Schedule, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Finance Report- Projection based on July to October Annuals, 2002; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Profits Information, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Investment Mtg, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Rockinlle Settlement, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - WPA/C, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Transition- Staff Attrition, circa 2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Sotheby's, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folders 1-5)
    - Investment Meeting, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folders 5-7)
    - WPA Corcoran, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folders 8-9)
    - Campaign- Background, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Endowment-Scholarships, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Restricted Funds, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Investment Policy, 1999; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Sanford Bernstein Endowment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - BGI Endowment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - McHugh Associated Endowment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - College - Facility Reg, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Curriculum, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Self-Study, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folders 19-20)
    - School Enrollment & Admissions, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Guardsmark, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Membership, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Authorized Signatures, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Endowment, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Parking, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Riggs Credit, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Budget Process, 2002; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Campaign, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Chillum Property Associates, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Washington Business Journal, 2001 July 13-19; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Calendar, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - PDS, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Health Care Costs, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Crime, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Investments Subcommittee, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - David Contract, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - HR Forms, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Chillum - Board Reg, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Bond Resolution, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Insurance, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Local Banks, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Bond Debt rating, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Jackie Plan, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Rockville, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Bond Issuance, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Civil Engineer Contract, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Jackie Show, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Development Reports, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - College Self-Study, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Insignia ESG, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Corcoran Views, 2002; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Ethical Guidelines, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Real Estate, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Misc. Correspondence, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Museum Publications, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Millennium Arts Center, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Corcoran Renovation, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folders 38-39)
    - Financial, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Corcoran Faculty Association, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - Board Retreat Summary, 1995; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 42)
    - Finance, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 43)
    - New England Pension Consultants, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 44)
    - Controller, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 45)
    - Controller Search, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 46)
    - Gehry, 1999 Nov; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folders 47-48)
    - Tysons, circa 1990s-2000s; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 49)
    - PWC Management Letter Comments, 2000; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 50)
    - Investment Performance, 1999-2001; Series 13 subseries 5 (Box 81, Folder 51)